Monika said, Amanda, you should be a songwriter.
So I have actually released four albums.
Life Experience, Spandex Rhymes and Soul,
Madame Monochrome, and Technicolor Lover.
And I had a poetry album called Never a Dull Moment.
And if you go on YouTube, you can look up some of my music.
The greatest song I've ever written is, in my opinion,
a song called Man Child.
And it was produced by the homie Ski,
who Ski Beats produced.
This is it, what?
Cuccini pouring from the sky.
Let's get rich, what?
Yeah.
So shout out to Ski Beats.
I'll give you a little acapella glimpse of the song.
Stuck in his way
Walking with his chest out
Knows what he ain't
But don't know what to be about
He understands
That he could be there
That he could move mountains
And be a go-getter
But he's a man child in a promised land
And I can't hold his hand
To make him see and make him comprehend
That it's all his for the taking
I've had several lives, y'all
The fin
I'll convince me
And I'll convince you
Toilated you